rap game Jeremy Hammond shown in the
lead I need something to do so I'm a
pack a bowl and drop some bars on you
you script kiddies ain't you can't
code can you you'll never guess that my
password is hunter - pecking with a
banana that so ripe no letters on
the keyboard so that you can't type fork
bomb who sanitize funny and code
and PHP and print out dollar side money
ah keep hacking alley Oh keep hacking
alley
Oh keep hacking elite Oh keep hacking
alley shouts out to my Truelove GrubHub
without them I'd be out trying to get
fed sitting on the top all over
your bunk bed drop deuces like I'm
Hollywood Undead I don't got a team I am
just one dude I don't pop Molly I rock
Tom Cruise